

CONTACT



+91-7382481437



annamdasuraghuram@gmail.com



https://deluxe-bublanina-57a938.netlify.app



10, 18th street, Tansi Nagar, Velacheri, Chennai - 600042

KEY SKILLS

- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- Java Script
- React JS
- Node JS/ Express JS
- Mongo DB
- Redux

LANGUAGES

- English
- Hindi
- Telugu

RAGHU RAM ANNAMDASU

MERN STACK DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

An enthusiastic and high-energy driven professional, targeting assignment in **Software Development** with an organization of repute. **M.Tech** (Power Systems, **IIT-Dhanbad**) qualified professional offered around 5 years of experience in Electrical design of Switchgear for Industrial plants.

EDUCATION

GUVI Geeks Network, Chennai (APR '22- Present)

MERN Full Stack Development Program

Indian Institute of Technology (IIT), Dhanbad (2015 - 2017)

M.Tech (Power Systems Engineering) - 9.1/10 CGPA

Andhra University, Visakhapatnam (2010 - 2014)

BE (Electrical & Electronics Engineering) - 9.22/10 CGPA

Board of Intermediate, Andhra Pradesh (2008 - 2010)

Intermediate (Mathematics, Physics & Chemistry) - 96.1%

Board of Secondary Education, AP (2007 - 2008)

SSC (10th Standard) - 91.2%

MAJOR PROJECTS

CAR RENTAL APPLICATION - A2Z Cars

Project link - https://mellifluous-dieffenbachia-fe1424.netlify.app Key skills used - React JS, Redux, HTML5, CSS3, Node JS. Express JS, Mongo DB, Material UI.

STUDENT DASHBOARD APPLICATION - Learn Infinity

Project link - https://frabjous-cheesecake-7e93d1.netlify.app
Key skills used - React JS, HTML5, CSS3, Node JS. Express JS, Mongo DB, Material UI.

STACK OVERFLOW CLONE APPLICATION

Project link - https://frabjous-maamoul-63a380.netlify.app
Key skills used - React JS, HTML5, CSS3, Node JS. Express JS, Mongo DB, Material UI.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Design Engineer - M/s L&T Construction

July 2017 - May 2021

Senior Proposals Engineer - M/s VA Tech Wabag

June 2021 - November 2021

Senior Associate Consultant - M/s Infosys

November 2021 - May 2022